

Business Analyst ~ 3 moe <u>£</u> 22/02/1999 **DUONG NGUYEN** O MBTI: INFJ

. 0946 292 494

O District 10, HCM City.

∇[•] duongnguyen.22@icloud.com

(a) darleigh.com | LinkedIn

Introduce

To become a true IT BA, there are many things that need to be done, especially regarding UX, such as writing documentation to complete a product. I believe that I have the qualities necessary to succeed. These qualities are demonstrated by my academic and extracurricular experiences.

Education

(2017-Expect 2023)

Bachelors, Ton Duc Thang University.

Software Engineering, GPA 7.2/10.

Class director: Good Rating.

Spiritual unity among 87 classmates to grow together in knowledge and common activities.

Certifications

IIBA Business Analyst Foundations Communicate

Google Project Management

Google UX Designer

Google Analytics

Google IT Python

IIG TOEIC R&L 530

Google Digital Marketing 9LX 7AB 5MF

Presentation

Critical Thinking

Problem Analysis

Decision-making Negotiation

Agile Foundations

Experience

VnResource (03/2023-Present)

Business Analyst • LMS Webapp • Agile Scrum

In charge of the current primary Business Analyst role for the **PVFCCO** project, which includes:

- Providing support in creating user guides.
- Assisting in tasks related to participating in building a gap list.

SBT LMS Project Experience and collaborate with Dev to build Gamification features.

Luong Thanh Phat Company (05/2022 - 08/2022)

Techinical Collaborator • Django • Waterfall

Web applications provide digital transformation and processization of contract administration, enhanced tram information, and car rental partners using software.

HongHanh Wedding Services - honghanh.net (05/2022 - Present)

Technical Co-Founder • Product Designer • Sales • Leadership • Waterfall

Applying digital transformation involves the use of cloud technologies in task management and work assignment to other jobs. Furthermore, self-employment allows me to better grasp the duties and processes involved in optimizing the efficiency of overtime labor.

Jobnet Vietnam (10/2020-02/2021)

UIX Designer Intern · Visual Designer · Webapp

In this employment, I was taught in fundamental programming abilities and website expertise, storing data about websites such as LandingPage, eCommerce.